Button, Daniel Evan; Papers apap231
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Case Files, 1965-1971; Undated; 5; 13.6 cubic ft.
  - Calabrece, Eugene, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 78)
  - Callahan, John H., 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 79)
  - Callahan, John P. - Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 80)
  - Cammer, Mrs. Howard - Postmaster appointment, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 81)
  - Cappielo, Dante - Veterans Administration, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 82)
  - Carl, Kenneth - Watervliet Arsenal, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 83)
  - Casale, Salvatore - Internal Revenue Service, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 84)
  - Casper, Anthony - Post Office Department, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 85)
  - Catena, Cornelius - ACOI, Albany, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 86)
  - Cavano, Herbert E. - Federal Communications Commission, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 87)
  - Cavano, J.E. - Navy, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 88)
  - Ceccucci, Gary V., 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 89)
  - Cesare, Vincent R. - Post Office Department, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 90)
  - C.F. Wnuk - Veterans and Civil Service, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 91)
  - Chambers, James H. - General Services Administration, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 92)
  - Charboneau, Raymond M. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 93)
  - Cheles, Pamela J. - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 94)
  - Chevalier, Alger - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 95)
  - Chiofolo, Albert, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 96)
  - Chiofolo, Sylvester P. - Veterans Administration, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 97)
  - Choi, Joseph J. - State Department, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 98)
  - Ciarnello, Joseph - National Guard / Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 99)
  - Chouiniere, Gregory - Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 100)
  - Ciani, Reverend Francis P., 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 101)
  - Clinchy, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 102)
  - Coffin, Robert G. - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 103)
  - Comfort, J.T. - State Department, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 104)
  - Commemorative Stamp of Dr. Martin Luther King Jr. - Post Office, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 105)
  - Corey, Dallas L. - Marine Corps, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 106)
  - Cornell, Robert W. - Marines - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 107)
  - Costante, Di Bernando - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 108)
  - Cook, James W. - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 109)
  - Coppola, Alessandro - State Department, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 110)
  - Couch, John A. - Air Force, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 111)
  - Craft, Bryan - Navy, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 112)
  - Crans, Milton H. - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 113)
  - Cronin, Michael F. - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 114)
  - Crounse, Michael A. - Post Office Department, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 115)
  - Crump, David - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 116)
  - Cummings, James A. - Senate Judiciary Commission, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 117)
  - Cunningham, John S. - Department of the Navy - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 118)
  - Cunningham, Rex J. - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 119)
  - Daly, Kathleen - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 120)
  - D'Ambrosio, Frank, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 121)
  - Danner, Ronald - Marines - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 122)
  - Davis, Robert - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 123)
  - Decheio, Mrs. Vincent - Watervliet Arsenal, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 124)
  - DeForge, Douglas and Kathleen - Internal Revenue Service, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 125)
  - DeForge, John - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 126)
  - De Graff, Bernard J. - Marines, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 127)
  - DeLaney, Dennis D. - Marines, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 128)
  - DeLuccia, Frank J. - Selective Service System, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 129)
  - DeVoe, Donald F. - Marine Corps, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 130)
  - DeWitt, Constance - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 131)
  - Dickershaid, Frank A. - Internal Revenue Service, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 132)
  - DiCocco, Ersilia, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 133)
  - Diehl, William F. - Selective Service System, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 134)
  - Dietz, Mrs. Leonard - Post Office, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 135)
  - DiFlorio, Francis J. - Post Office, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 136)
  - Dillon, James - Department of Health, Education and Welfare, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 137)
  - Dimeo, Isadore - Immigration, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 138)
  - Dixon, Maynard - Selective Service System, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 139)
  - Dolan, Kenneth J. - Civil Service Commission, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 140)
  - Donovan, Martin J. Jr. - Department of Labor, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 141)
  - Dowsland, T/Sgt David G. - Air Force, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 142)
  - Dozios, Robert J. - Marine Corps, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 143)
  - Drake, Ralph - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 144)
  - Dunlap, John F. - Public Health Service, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 145)
  - Dziarcak, Leo - Marine Corps, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 146)
  - Ellis, David J. - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 147)
  - Emery, John - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 148)
  - Engle, Peter C. - Navy, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 149)
  - Erwin, John M. - Internal Revenue Service, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 150)
  - Fairway Supermarket shopping center - Post Office, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 151)
  - Farnham, Lawrence E. - Army, Emergency Leave, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 152)
  - Faulkner, Paul - Blair House Fine Arts Committee, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 153)
  - Feinman - State Department, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 154)
  - Feller, Richard N. - Selective Service System, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 155)
  - Ferrara, Rufus J. - Immigration, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 156)
  - Figuerroa, Armando B. - Immigration and National Service, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 157)
  - Filippine, Julie - Selective Service System, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 158)
  - Finn, Stephen A. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1968; 1969 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 159)
  - Fisher, Frank - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 160)
  - Fleres, Anthony - Navy, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 161)
  - Flick, John - State, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 162)
  - Flynn, Seaman Robert E. - Navy, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 163)
  - Francis, Paul - Army, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 164)
  - Francis, Wallace C. - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 165)
  - Francois, Dale T. - Navy, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 166)
  - Frangella, Carmen, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 167)
  - Franz, Joseph - Navy, 1968 (Box 6 (5-Case Files), Folder 168)
  - Frazier, Garry Patrick, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 1)
  - French, Walter H. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 2)
  - Fritz, Andrew - Post Office, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 3)
  - Gabriel, George W. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 4)
  - Gans, Bruce, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 5)
  - Gardner, David L. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 6)
  - Gardner, Raymond - Navy, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 7)
  - Gaughan, Harold E. - HEW, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 8)
  - Gernhardt, Reverend Arthur H. - Immigration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 9)
  - Giampa, Joseph A. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 10)
  - Gill, James R. - Social Security, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 11)
  - Ginsburgh, Louis, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 12)
  - Godden, Mary Anne - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 13)
  - Goldstein, Donald A. - Securities and Exchange Commission, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 14)
  - Goman, Paul - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 15)
  - Gordon, Ethel - State, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 16)
  - Gorman, Louis - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 17)
  - Gorman, Louis - Marine Corps, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 18)
  - Graham, Warren L. - Civil Service Commission, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 19)
  - Granlees, Clara - Social Security Administration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 20)
  - Gray, Chester - Veterans Administration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 21)
  - Greene, William M. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 22)
  - Grimmer, Dr. George - Social Security Administration - HEW - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 23)
  - Grogan, Albert F. - Internal Revenue Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 24)
  - Guerrero, Rosario - Department of State, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 25)
  - Guffin, Mildred - Immigration and National Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 26)
  - Guilianelli, Mary - Veterans Administration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 27)
  - Hagarty, James - Post Office Department, 1968; 1969 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 28)
  - Harrison, Bill - Internal Revenue Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 29)
  - Harrison, William - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 30)
  - Hartheimer, Albert S. - New Albany Postal Facilities, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 31)
  - Haver, Wallace L. - Navy, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 32)
  - Haverly, Bertha L. - State Department, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 33)
  - Harwood, Alexander P. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 34)
  - Hazzard, Raymond - Department of Labor, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 35)
  - Heldeberg Bluestone & Marble Inc., 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 36)
  - Heldeberg workshop, Voorheesville - special bulk mailing permit, approved, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 37)
  - Hendrickson, Matthew I. - Social Security Administration - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 38)
  - Hibbard, E.I. - New York State problem, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 39)
  - Hicken, T.L. - Post Office, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 40)
  - Hill, Charles U. Jr. - Employment, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 41)
  - Hilt, Donald - Air Force, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 42)
  - Hinman, George J. - Army 1018th, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 43)
  - Hitchcock, Peter Blake - Air Force, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 44)
  - Hofmann, Edward - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 45)
  - Horan, Bart J. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 46)
  - Houst, Douglas R. - Schenectady referral, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 47)
  - Howard, Burton - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 48)
  - Hurley, Richard J. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 49)
  - Hutton, Linda I. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 50)
  - Ingram, Marilyn - Civil Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 51)
  - Imelda, Sister M. - Dominican Retreat House (Cuban Refugee Program), 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 52)
  - Johnson, Larry - Veterans Administration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 53)
  - Jones, Allan - Watervliet Arsenal, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 54)
  - Jones, Marie E. - Navy, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 55)
  - Jones, Robert E. - Navy, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 56)
  - Jones, Stephen E. - Selective Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 57)
  - Jorgensen, John Christian - [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 58)
  - Juliano, Steven - Air Force, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 59)
  - Kanches, Peter - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 60)
  - Keane, John J. - Veterans Administration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 61)
  - Keely, James W. - Internal Revenue Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 62)
  - Kehoe, Peter L. - Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1968-1969 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 63)
  - Kelly, James D. - Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1968; 1969 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 64)
  - Kemp, Dennis - Marines, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 65)
  - Kennedy, William - HEW, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 66)
  - Kenney, Richard E. - Navy, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 67)
  - Kerker, Harry J. - Selective Service System, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 68)
  - Khatar, Antoine J. - Immigration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 69)
  - Kindt, Henry G. - Commerce Department, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 70)
  - Klein, Carl J. - Marines, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 71)
  - Knapp, Edward - Civil Service Commission, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 72)
  - Kniffen, Paul - Navy, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 73)
  - Korbel, Mark A. - Immigration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 74)
  - Kowall, Douglas - Marines, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 75)
  - Kowalski, Joseph - Veterans, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 76)
  - Kranick, George J. - Small Business Administration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 77)
  - Krimsky, Mrs. Phillip - Department of Labor, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 78)
  - Kristoffersen, Ernest - Treasury Department, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 79)
  - Ku, Henry F.H. - Albany Medical College, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 80)
  - Kurasik, Steve - Social Security, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 81)
  - Lail, Dan M. - Air Force, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 82)
  - Lambert, Raymond B., 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 83)
  - Langlois, David - Navy, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 84)
  - Lasak, Lubomir S. - Immigration and National Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 85)
  - Latella, Dennis - New York State matter, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 86)
  - Lauterborn, Raymond J., 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 87)
  - LaValle, Raoul V., 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 88)
  - Laversee, Gordon - Internal Revenue Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 89)
  - Lawlor, John, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 90)
  - Lawry, David A. - Immigration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 91)
  - Leach, Howard H. - Citizens Bank and Trust, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 92)
  - Leahey, Richard T. - Air Force, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 93)
  - Leclerq, Phillippe G. - Immigration and National Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 94)
  - Lee, Mary - Defense, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 95)
  - Lemon, Alfred F. - General Services Administration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 96)
  - Lennon, Mrs. Bernard J. - Veterans Administration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 97)
  - Leonard, Edward G. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 98)
  - Leonard, John P. - Air Force, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 99)
  - Leroy, Alfred - Post Office Department, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 100)
  - Lester, Howard L. - Public Service Commission, Albany, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 101)
  - Levey, Margaret - Treasury Department, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 102)
  - Lewis, Paul W. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 103)
  - Leyden, John Charles - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 104)
  - Lezzi, Louis J. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 105)
  - Liddle, Charles M. III - Post Office Department, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 106)
  - Linders, Larry - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 107)
  - Lirio, Dr. Oscar C. - Immigration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 108)
  - Livingston, James and Katherine, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 109)
  - Lomenzo, John, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 110)
  - Longton, Robert G. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 111)
  - Lot, O. Yuet - Immigration and National Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 112)
  - Lotho, Remedios C. - Immigration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 113)
  - Loucks, John - Air Force, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 114)
  - Love, William J. - Veterans Administration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 115)
  - Loveday, Victor - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 116)
  - Lovell, Charles A. - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 117)
  - Lyndon, Everett C. - Veterans Administration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 118)
  - Mackay, David B. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 119)
  - 727th Maintenance BN Co. "B" (Cohoes) - National Guard, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 120)
  - Maloney, Jane - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 121)
  - Maloney, Reverend Thomas J. - Immigration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 122)
  - Manley, John T. - Marines, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 123)
  - Manning, Peter - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 124)
  - Mannino, Lena - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 125)
  - Manpower Developing Training Act Projects - Department of Labor, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 126)
  - Marchesi, Joseph L. - Navy, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 127)
  - Marsala, Guy M. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 128)
  - Marticke, Roger - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 129)
  - Martin, B. - Selective Service System, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 130)
  - Martin, Nellie - Social Security Administration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 131)
  - Martini, Vera - Trans World Airlines, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 132)
  - Maya, Waldemar D. Jr. - Air Force, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 133)
  - McCarthy, Donald F. Jr. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 134)
  - McClurg, Jo Ann L. - Internal Revenue Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 135)
  - McDonald, Rendle J., 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 136)
  - McGlynn, William J. - Post Office, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 137)
  - McGovern, Thomas - HEW, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 138)
  - Mebel, Peter E. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 139)
  - Meikle, John W.H. - Federal Communications Commission, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 140)
  - Mercier, Guy - Marines, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 141)
  - Miazga, Phillip - Army - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 142)
  - Micare, Joseph - Marines, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 143)
  - Middleton, Thomas - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 144)
  - Milhizer, Helen G. - Navy, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 145)
  - Miller, Paul Allan - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 146)
  - Miller, Clarence D. - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 147)
  - Minehardt, Allen Lee - Navy, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 148)
  - Misiewics, Raymond - Selective Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 149)
  - Misuraca, Robert C. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 150)
  - Mohrmann, Arthur - Marines, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 151)
  - Monaco, Joseph M. - President's Commission on Violence, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 152)
  - Monda, Jamel - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 153)
  - Monteiro, J.P. Machado - Immigration and National Service, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 154)
  - Moon, Donald - Department of Agriculture, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 155)
  - Moon, William C. - Veterans Administration, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 156)
  - Moore, John L. - Blue Cross Blue Shield - Albany - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 157)
  - Moore, William - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 158)
  - Morelli, Albert E. Jr. - New York State Bar Association, Albany, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 159)
  - Morlock, Joseph E. - Army, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 160)
  - Morse, Richard D. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 161)
  - Mosall, Ronald - Navy, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 162)
  - Mott, John R. - Post Office, 1968 (Box 7 (5-Case Files), Folder 163)
  - Motta, Michael A. - West Point - [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 1)
  - Muller, Otto, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 2)
  - Murphy, Edward Jr. - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 3)
  - Murphy, James M. - Air Force - [RESTRICTED], 1968-1970 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 4)
  - Murray, David J. - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 5)
  - Murray, Richard - Department of Motor Vehicles, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 6)
  - Neals, Edward J. - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 7)
  - New Casework, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 8)
  - Nicoll, Joseph J. - Interstate Commerce Commission, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 9)
  - Nimh, Rosine - State Department, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 10)
  - Noiseux, Walter C. - Veterans, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 11)
  - Odza, Mitchell A. - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 12)
  - O'Malley, Carol A. - Internal Revenue Service/Treasury Department, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 13)
  - O'Rourke, Samuel - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 14)
  - Ortal, Yolanda A., 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 15)
  - Palmer, Delores - Internal Revenue Service, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 16)
  - Palmer, Leonard M. - Civil Service Commission, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 17)
  - Palmier Oil Company, Inc. - Department of Labor, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 18)
  - Palmiotto, Vincent M. - Internal Revenue Service, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 19)
  - Pardi, Hannibal Esq. - State Department, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 20)
  - Pardi, Laurence - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 21)
  - Parks, William, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 22)
  - Pasquariello, Arthur A. - Selective Service System, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 23)
  - Pawl, Mrs. Laurence - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 24)
  - Pepsi-Cola Albany Bottling Company, Inc., 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 25)
  - Philatelic Sales Unit, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 26)
  - Pickett, John J. - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 27)
  - Pierce, Ray W. - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 28)
  - Pillig, Richard E. - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 29)
  - Pitcherello, Steve - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 30)
  - Polish American Veterans WWII - Department of Defense, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 31)
  - Polsinelli, Vito E. - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 32)
  - Post Office - boxes for New York State Health Department, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 33)
  - Priess, Gustav - Immigration and National Service, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 34)
  - Proposed postal facilities - Albany, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 35)
  - Prothero, Scott - Navy, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 36)
  - Prudente, Stephen - West Point, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 37)
  - Puczek, Paul - Department of State, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 38)
  - Purdy, James A. - Department of State, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 39)
  - Pusateri, Richard A. - Annapolis - [RESTRICTED], 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 40)
  - Queeney, Richard - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 41)
  - Ranney, Stephen - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 42)
  - Rasher, George - HEW, Social Security Administration, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 43)
  - Raugh, B. Michael Esq., 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 44)
  - Reilly, Peter H. - Army, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 45)
  - Richardson, Ronald - Department of State/Immigration, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 46)
  - Richburg, John E. - taxi licensing, 1968 (Box 8 (5-Case Files), Folder 47)